<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="changelog">
        &lt;b&gt;0.13.0 (Dec 1, 2020)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Polish translation added by WaldiS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - French translation added by J. Lavoie.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Norwegian translation updated by Allan Nordhøy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - German translation updated by Simon Kreuzer and J. Lavoie.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.12.0 (Mar 25, 2020)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Add location permissions for Android 10. Android 10 requires fine instead of coarse
        location permission to access the WiFi SSID. And it need it \'all the time\' to be able
        to use SSID whitelist while AN2Linux is running in background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.11.0 (Oct 25, 2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Norwegian (bokmål) translation by bilde2910, thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.10.0 (Oct 9, 2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Add support for commas in WiFi SSID&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.9.2 (Sep 4, 2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Add information about battery optimizations (Doze) introduced in Android 6.0.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.9.0 (Sep 1, 2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Add support for filtering apps with text search in \'Enabled applications\' settings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Add quick settings tile for toggle enable/disable AN2Linux.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Change minimum version required from Android 4.4 (API 19) to Android 4.3 (API 18).&lt;br&gt;
        Title/message extraction from notification was added in API 19, which
        means that it will not be supported for Android 4.3 users. It might
        still be possible to extract title/message with reflection however (or in some other way).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New setting: don\'t send notification if phone display is turned on.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.8.1 (Feb 26, 2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Fix build bug which is stopping F-Droid, now disable error on lint. Thank you edaubert!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - German translation by Luensche, thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.8.0 (May 26, 2018)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - From Android 8.1 COARSE_LOCATION permission is needed to access WiFi SSID! Also it seems
        that location services needs to be turned on as well, otherwise the SSID reported will
        be \"unknown ssid\".&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Setting to run AN2Linux as a foreground service, thank you Eyenseo!&lt;br&gt;
        Android 8.0 added \'Background Execution Limits\' to help with battery drain caused by apps
        running in background. Which means that AN2Linux might be killed by the system. So if you
        run Android Oreo+ and have problems with AN2Linux missing notifications, then you could try
        to run AN2Linux as a foreground service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Dutch translation by Vistaus, thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Spanish translation by CalebCDE, thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.7.0 (Jan 16, 2018)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New icon created by conrad-heimbold@github, thank you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.6.0 (May 12, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New preference added for minimum notification priority&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.5.1 (Apr 12, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Fix bug that caused AN2Linux to crash when opening individual app settings (affecting Android 4.4-5.1)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.5.0 (Apr 5, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Replace sha1 with sha256&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.4.0 (Apr 1, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Allow notification settings to be set individually per app&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.3.0 (Feb 6, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New preference added for custom icon size&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.2.0 (Jan 9, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - New preference added for Android 5.0+ Lollipop users: "Block local notifications"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.1.1 (Jan 7, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Fix bug that made AN2Linux unusable for Android 4.4 KitKat users (using ciphers not supported until 5.0)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;0.1.0 (Jan 2, 2017)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
        - Initial release
    </string>
</resources>
